PROFILE

An efficient MERN stack web developer with an intuition for both system and UI design. Adept in improvising and adapting to challenges, with a proclivity to constantly optimize using creative approaches. Very research-oriented and thorough in her methods. Would like to bring her passion to any organization that appreciates it and presents ample intellectual challenges.

PROJECTS

Rimessa 🖪

Githuh 17

Ecommerce website for luxury fashion apparels.

A solo project - built & executed in 5 days

Features:

- Responsive, dark mode supported, theming
- Carousals, cart, filtering, sorting, pagination
- User login/register
- Query strings & routing

Tech stack: Chakra UI | ReactJS | JSON Server

Musk Meds 🛮

Github 🖪

Ecommerce website for medical and health products. A collaborative Project of 4 members - built and executed in 5 days

Features:

- Login/Register, Sticky & functional navbar, admin panel, Landing page
- Products page, functional category links, cart (my tasks)
- Dynamic filtering, sorting, pagination (my tasks)
- Searchbars, fetching medicines by first letter (my tasks)

Areas of Responsibility:

- Led the team by planning the workflow, delegating tasks & coordinating
- Conducted daily meets, debugged and resolved roadblocks
- Set up the server, acquired data
- Took over javascript heavy tasks: API calls, OOP, debouncing
- streamlined the code, reduced redundancy

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Advanced JS | JSON Server

Myntra Clone 🛮

Github 🛭

Ecommerce website for clothing and accessories.

A solo project - built and executed in 4 days

Features:

- Mens & womens products page
- Dynamic filtering, sorting, pagination
- User login/register (localstorage)
- Product details, cart & wishlist

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Vanilla JS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Research Intern, Spartificial

11/2022 - present

Working on a mentored land segmentation research project.

Intern, Shankus Medicity (Paediatric Neuro Center)

10/2019 – 11/2019 | Mehsana, Gujarat

Conducted psychological mapping, audits & training; built protocols.

Madhurima Poddar Full Stack Web Developer



RimRaider639 Rortfolio

in Madhurima Poddar

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Masai School 08/2022 - present

Bachelors of Computer Applications, Amrita Vishwa Vidyapeetham 07/2021 – present | Coimbatore

A Levels, Divine Child International School 04/2019 - 03/2021 | Ahmedabad

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python | JS | TS | ReactJS | HTML | CSS OOP | SQL | DSA | NextJS | Chakra UI Web Scraping | JAVA | Pandas | Numpy ML | Github | Digital Image Processing Computer Vision | Testing | Redux

SOFT SKILLS

Research | Organization | Critical Thinking Remote Work

ACHIEVMENTS

Certified in Astronomical Data Science, Spartificial

Machine Learning for Physics Application, Spartificial

Complete Python Bootcamp, *Udemy*

Led the 3rd Top Team - Lunathon (Hackathon), Spartificial with ISRO

✓ INTERESTS

Sketching & Painting | Programming Games Building ML/DL Models | Brain Science